{"description":"Default","name":"Sampling Distributions","questions":[{"correct":1,"image_data":[],"options":["0.01","0.04","0.10","0.11"],"question":"A high school swim team 50 meter freestyle is normally distributed with a mean time of 33 seconds and a standard deviation of 1.67. If 30 seconds is considered to be a fast time let X = the time of a randomly selected swimmer from the team who is considered a fast swimmer."},{"correct":2,"image_data":[],"options":["II. Only","III. Only","I. and III.","I. and II."],"question":"Which of the following are biased estimators?\nI. Sample Means\nII. Sample proportions\nIII. Sample Variance"},{"correct":0,"image_data":[],"options":["0.08","0.17","0.24","0.32"],"question":"A coin is tossed 15 times. What is the probability of getting 4 heads?"},{"correct":3,"image_data":[],"options":["0.01","0.07","0.12","0.20"],"question":"A student is taking a quiz that has 16 true and false questions. What is the probability of the student receiving exactly 8 questions correct?"},{"correct":2,"image_data":[],"options":["Mean = 0.215; Standard deviation = 0.02","Mean = 0.215; Standard deviation = 0.16","Mean = 0.215; Standard deviation = 0.18","Mean = 0.215; Standard deviation = 1.09"],"question":"In a pack of multicolored straws about 21.5 percent are red. Each time seven straws are pulled out with replacement. What are the mean and standard deviation of the sampling distribution of the sample proportion of blue straws for samples of size seven?"},{"correct":1,"image_data":[],"options":["Is independent with a larger sample size","Increases with a larger sample size","Decreases with a larger sample size","Depends on the sample size"],"question":"The standard error of the sample mean ___."},{"correct":0,"image_data":[],"options":["0.02","0.03","0.04","0.07"],"question":"In a random sample of 390 people, the proportion of people who don't own a pet is 0.24. What is the standard deviation of the sample proportion?"},{"correct":2,"image_data":[],"options":["0.11","0.23","0.49","0.55"],"question":"The time it takes for most sudoku players to complete a medium level is normally distributed about 4.5 minutes with a standard deviation 0.67 minutes. Find the probability that a randomly chosen person will take less than 4 minutes to complete the puzzle."},{"correct":3,"image_data":[],"options":["II. only","III. only","I. and III. ","II. and III."],"question":"Which of the following is true?\nI. The sum of population standard deviations is equal to the difference of two means \nII. The difference of two means is equal to the difference of population means\nIII. The larger the sample, the spread becomes smaller in the sampling distribution."},{"correct":0,"image_data":[],"options":["Population: All americans who wear sunscreen; Parameter: proportion of Americans who don’t wear sunscreen at all","Population: All americans; Parameter: all Americans who don’t wear sunscreen at all","Population: All americans who wear sunscreen; Parameter: proportion of Americans who wear sunscreen during the summer months","Population: All americans; Parameter: proportion of americans who wear sunscreen"],"question":"Only 31% of Americans say they wear sunscreen all-year round. This leaves 1 in 10 people who don't wear sunscreen at all. Based on the problem, identify the population and parameters."}]}